

TIARA YULINDA PUTRI

FRESH GRADUATE

SKILLS

Programming Skill:

- HTML, CSS, JS
- PHP
- Laravel
- Vb NET.
- MySQL

Software Skill:

- Figma (UI/UX)
- Ms. Office
- Ms. Visio

CONTACT

Ponsel & WA: +62 813-9887-1645 Mail: tiarayulindaputri98@gmail.com

SOCIAL

Github: github.com/TiaraYulinda LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/tiara-yulinda Portofolio: https://tiarayulinda.github.io/

ABOUT ME

I am a Bachelor of Information System. I am a 22 years old, female. I graduated from STMIK Insan Pembangunan. I have the ability to create programs with PHP using the laravel framework. I have a good responsibility with task. Able to work in team or individually.

EDUCATION

Majoring in Information System

STMIK Insan Pembangunan | 2016 - 2020

- GPA 3.65
- Member of Executive Council Of Student

Senior High School

SMAN 19 Kab. Tangerang | 2013-2016

- Final Exam Score 84.6

NON-FORMAL

Intro To Full Stack Developer

Program FGA DTS Kominfo | Augustus 2021

Computer Operator Assistant

UPTD Latihan Kerja Kab. Tangerang | July 2021

Womenderful Bootocamp - SQL

Progate | March 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. Paragon Technology and Innovation

Production Operator | July 2020 - Oct 2020

• Ensure the quality of the products made

PT.EDS Manufacturing Indonesia

Production Operator | May, 2018 - June, 2019

- Ensure the quality of the products made
- Make product without defect

PROJECT

-E-learning for assigment | e-learning-ipem.epizy.com